Hello Terps, the University of Maryland has earned our reputation as one of the premier
universities in the world.
We are approaching 70 members of the prestigious national academies among our faculty and have
nearly 50 members of the American Association for the Advancement of Science.
Our students earned more than 100 major national and international awards last year, including
54 students and scholars who accepted Fulbright grants.
This week, U.S. News and World Report released its annual college rankings and the University
of Maryland ranked 19th among all U.S. public universities.
Additionally, we now have almost 70 schools, colleges, programs and specialties on the
U.S. News Top 25 lists.
Our excellence extends well beyond our nationally recognized academic programs.
Number 1 School for LGBTQ Plus Students
A top school for entrepreneurship, for veterans and for research.
And we were also recognized as one of the best places to work by both Newsweek Magazine
and Forbes Magazine.
Collectively, these rankings fill me with tremendous pride and I hope they make you proud of your
flagship university.
These rankings are important, but more importantly are what they represent.
Rankings are not merely numbers, they are a reflection of our commitments and our priorities,
including our focus on building academic and research excellence, fostering a welcoming
multicultural community, creating an innovative and entrepreneurial culture and investing
in people and communities.
It is extremely gratifying to see these investments and priorities being reflected in national
and international rankings.
When we pursue excellence in all we do, the University of Maryland continues our upward
trajectory.
And that's something we can all be proud of.
Go Terps!