Today we are so excited to welcome thousands of University of Maryland students as we all
come together united under one cause.
Turpan is the largest student-run philanthropy in the state of Maryland.
We raise funds and awareness for Children's National Health System.
We're here at the Army today where we all pledge to stand for 12 hours to honor the
patients and families at Children's National Health System.
We spend all year caring for these kids, caring for the hospital, and the most incredible
thing is to see 3,000 students coming together and supporting the hospital, supporting the
kids.
It's not a feeling you can describe.
Back in 2010, Brooke was about to turn two.
Brooke was treated at Children's National Medical Center for Acute Myeloid Leukemia, and Caitlin
actually was her donor, gave her bone marrow to cure her cancer, and so they asked us to
get involved in fundraising, and they invited us to Turpan.
The girls come here, they get treated like rock stars.
To Turpan, I actually host events all year round to raise money for the kids at the hospital,
and that's everything from hosting a festival of hope color on earlier this year, blood
drives, the whole line yards.
I am so proud and so inspired by Turpan.
One of Turpan's biggest missions has always been to create this culture of philanthropy
on campus.
And now that the University of Maryland is the Do Good University, we are so excited
to be surrounded by people on campus whose priority is philanthropy.