We had kids whose last hot meal was Friday lunch at school and they didn't eat over the weekend
until they got to Monday breakfast at school. That is not uncommon in Montgomery County where
8.9 percent of its residents were food insecure in 2021. County Executive Mark Elridge says that
three years later, not much has changed. The lines of people waiting for food have not gone away.
And it isn't a lack of food that's the problem. It's the waste of food. Americans throw away
nearly 40 percent of goods bought each year. That's like having 10 chicken nuggets and throwing
four away. And that adds up to nearly 149 billion meals getting thrown away each year in this country
according to Feed in America. To stop food waste, Montgomery County is partnered with
Mana Food Center. They say in addition to collecting food, one of their biggest challenges
is educating people. It's really to make a cultural shift in the nation around food waste. To
first bring people to an awareness about the scope of the problem and then to also offer
tips about how to both again reduce that food waste in your own home. Montgomery County
Environmental Protection Director John Monger says to make change, you don't have to change much.
You can start in your very own kitchen with your own shopping list, with your own meal prep,
with your own food storage, and it matters. It matters to our environment. Elridge knows
that change is hard, but he hopes Montgomery County can show others how it's done. Montgomery
County is not going to change the trajectory of the planet, but Montgomery County can be an example.
For CNS TV, I'm Alex Gary.